Text functions modify or provide information about text strings that we find in data.
文本函数修改数据中的文本字符串 或为其提供信息
A text string is a series of characters such as letters,
文本字符串由一系列的字符组成
numbers, and punctuation that is not treated like a number.
这些字符包括不被看作是数字的字母、数字和标点符号
Examples of text or text strings are; names,
文本或文本字符串示例包括
phrases, cities, countries, not a date or a number.
名称、短语、城市、国家、非日期或数字
There are many text functions in spreadsheets.
电子表格中有很多文本函数
We're going to go through a useful subset of these starting with the Substitute Function.
我们将讲解一些实用的文本函数 先从 SUBSTITUTE 函数开始
This is different from the find and replace tools we looked at in the previous lesson.
它与我们之前见到的查找/替换功能不一样
Those were used to make fundamental changes to values that exist in cells.
查找/替换用来对单元格中现有的值 进行基本的更改
In that case, the original information was destroyed and replaced.
也就是说 原始信息会被销毁和替换
When using a substitute function,
在使用 SUBSTITUTE 函数时
the original data remains intact.
原始数据保持不变
It's just transformed in a new location that we create.
只是转到我们创建的新位置
Let's take a closer look at how to do this.
我们看看如何使用该函数
I have a string,
有一个字符串
the quick brown fox,
“The quick brown fox”
and I want to replace brown with red.
我想将“brown”替换为“red”
There are a couple of ways that you can enter a formula in Excel and I'll go over both.
你可以通过多种方式在 Excel 中输入公式 我两种都介绍
One way is to use the formula bar.
一种是使用公式栏
Select your cell, then click the fx button on the formula bar.
选择单元格 然后点击公式栏中的 fx 按钮
You notice that it automatically enters the equal sign to get you started.
你会发现它自动输入了等号
A dialog will appear with the menu of functions and a search box.
接着出现一个对话框 其中包含函数菜单和搜索框
Select the function you want and click okay.
选择你想要的函数并点击确定
Another dialog will appear with boxes for entering the function parameters.
出现另一个对话框 用于输入函数参数
There's also some helpful information.
还有一些实用信息
For the substitute function,
对于 SUBSTITUTE 函数
the first parameter box is for the text,
第一个参数方框是文本 (Text)
which means the text we're searching on.
也就是在其中搜索的文本
The sentence in A1 for this example.
这里是 A1 中的句子
You can type A1 or select the cell directly.
你可以输入 A1 或直接选择该单元格
The next box is for the old text which is brown,
下个方框用于输入旧文本 (Old_text) 即“brown”
and then a box for the new text which is red.
然后是输入新文本的方框 (New_text) 即“red”
Finally, there is a box for the instance number,
最后的方框的输入表示替换第几个 (Instance num)
which is an optional parameter.
这是可选参数
I'll leave this blank to indicate I want all occurrences to be substituted.
我将留空 表示替换所有的相关文本
And we see that my new result is a sentence where brown has been replaced with red.
我们看到新的结果是“brown”替换成了“red”的句子
Notice that this dialog also automatically put my old and new values in quotes.
注意 这个对话框还自动将旧值和新值放在了引号里
The second way to do this is more direct and a little faster.
第二种方式更直接 也更快速
Select the cell you want and just start typing the formula,
选择单元格 然后开始输入公式
starting with the equal sign.
以等号开始
A list appears trying to autocomplete what you've typed.
然后出现一个自动填充列表
Click tab to select the highlighted function.
按下 Tab 键选择突出显示的函数
Now we see a helpful prompt showing function parameters
现在出现了帮助提示 显示函数参数
with the first parameter highlighted and optional parameters shown in brackets.
第一个参数高亮显示 可选参数用方括号表示
Click the cell for the first parameter then
点击第一个参数的单元格
type the comma to move onto the next parameter.
然后输入逗号 转到下个参数
Notice that you need to type the double quotes
注意 对于此方法
yourself for the text values with this method.
你需要手动为文本值输入双引号
Just close the print seize and click enter,
输入右括号 然后按下 Enter 键
and you've entered all the required parameters.
输入了所有必要的参数